export const quizData = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    option1: "45°",
    option2: "90°",
    option3: "60°",
    correctAnswer: "90°"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    option1: "obtuse",
    option2: "acute",
    option3: "right angled",
    correctAnswer: "right angled"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "A triangle can have",
    option1: "one right angle",
    option2: "two right angle",
    option3: "three right angle",
    correctAnswer: "one right angle"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?",
    option1: "14, 15, 26",
    option2: "12, 16, 20",
    option3: "16, 18, 20",
    correctAnswer: "12, 16, 20"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following triangles are always similar?",
    option1: "equilateral triangle",
    option2: "isosceles triangle",
    option3: "scalene Triangle",
    correctAnswer: "equilateral triangle"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "If one angle of a triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of remaining angles?",
    option1: "100°",
    option2: "85°",
    option3: "90°",
    correctAnswer: "100°"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "If the largest angle in a triangle is 70°, what is the least possible value of the smallest angle of the triangle?",
    option1: "30°",
    option2: "10°",
    option3: "40°",
    correctAnswer: "30°"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is",
    option1: "a + b + c",
    option2: "2a",
    option3: "None of these",
    correctAnswer: "a + b + c"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry",
    option1: "two",
    option2: "no",
    option3: "15",
    correctAnswer: "no"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "There is a right triangle PQR where: angle Q = 90°; angle P = angle R. What is the measure of angles P and R?",
    option1: "85°",
    option2: "65°",
    option3: "45°",
    correctAnswer: "45°"
  }
];
